<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://azurepx.com/</id>
    <title>Azure Blog</title>
    <updated>2024-02-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://azurepx.com/"/>
    <subtitle>Azure Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://azurepx.com/img/transgender_flag.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Trip to Guangzhou]]></title>
        <id>https://azurepx.com/2024/2/20/a-trip-to-guangzhou</id>
        <link href="https://azurepx.com/2024/2/20/a-trip-to-guangzhou"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I went to Guangzhou by bus on the 19th of February, the day before the one-day therapy session. The journey from Shenzhen to Guangzhou took around 3 hours. I felt a mix of nervousness and excitement. The hotel I stayed in was budget-friendly, but the room was quite small. Nevertheless, I only needed to stay there for one night. After taking a shower and preparing for the next day, I went to bed early, knowing that I had to wake up early for the therapy session.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I went to Guangzhou by bus on the 19th of February, the day before the one-day therapy session. The journey from Shenzhen to Guangzhou took around 3 hours. I felt a mix of nervousness and excitement. The hotel I stayed in was budget-friendly, but the room was quite small. Nevertheless, I only needed to stay there for one night. After taking a shower and preparing for the next day, I went to bed early, knowing that I had to wake up early for the therapy session.</p>
<p>It was a one day therapy session, I reached the hospital at 7:40am, the doctor was not there yet, my appointment is at 8:10am. I was feeling nervous and excited at the same time. I was the second one to arrive. There was a girl who was just like me was also waiting for the doctor. She was wearing a white top and a beautiful long skirt, with long black hair that reached her shoulders. Her exquisite makeup and confident expression added to her charm.</p>
<p>As I looked at myself in the mirror, I couldn't help but feel a twinge of insecurity and sadness. "If only I could be as confident as her," I thought to myself.</p>
<p>I dare not to look at her again, I was afraid that she would notice me staring at her. I took out my phone and started to chat with friends to distract myself.</p>
<p>Finally, the doctor arrived. She was called in first.</p>
<p>I was called in later and the doctor asked me a lot of questions, I answered them one by one. The doctor checked my breasts and said that they were growing well and healthily. I was so happy to hear that. Also, I was asked to take a blood test, and the result was good. The doctor said that I could taking the hormone therapy with a higher dose.</p>
<p>By the time I left the hospital, it was already 11:30am. I took a lunch at a nearby restaurant and then went to the next hospital to take the voice therapy. The doctor there was very professional and patient. She taught me how to speak in a more feminine way, it was the last session of the voice therapy.</p>
<p>After the therapy, I went to the bus station and took the bus back to Shenzhen. I was so tired that I fell asleep on the bus. I woke up when the bus arrived at the Shenzhen station. I took a taxi back home and went to bed early.</p>
<p>It was a long day, but I felt happy and satisfied. I was one step closer to becoming the person I wanted to be. I was grateful for the progress I had made and was looking forward to the next therapy session.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Azure Pan</name>
            <email>azurepan213@gmail.com</email>
            <uri>https://github.com/azurepx</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="hrt" term="hrt"/>
        <category label="therapy" term="therapy"/>
        <category label="guangzhou" term="guangzhou"/>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Learn Algorithms?]]></title>
        <id>https://azurepx.com/2024/2/4/why-learn-algorithms</id>
        <link href="https://azurepx.com/2024/2/4/why-learn-algorithms"/>
        <updated>2024-02-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four key points]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Four key points</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>Solve computational problems</li>
<li>Prove correctioness</li>
<li>Argue efficiency</li>
<li>Communication</li>
</ol>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Azure Pan</name>
            <email>azurepan213@gmail.com</email>
            <uri>https://github.com/azurepx</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="algorithms" term="algorithms"/>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hospital Visit]]></title>
        <id>https://azurepx.com/2023/10/25/hospital</id>
        <link href="https://azurepx.com/2023/10/25/hospital"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I only slept for three hours last night, but I'm doing fine. On the way to Guangzhou Overseas Chinese Hospital, I told myself that today would be an extraordinary day, the first time I would talk about my own matters face to face, the first time in my life, hoping not to have any regrets.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I only slept for three hours last night, but I'm doing fine. On the way to Guangzhou Overseas Chinese Hospital, I told myself that today would be an extraordinary day, the first time I would talk about my own matters face to face, the first time in my life, hoping not to have any regrets.</p>
<p>As expected, the communication with the doctor went smoothly, without much hesitation or pain. I calmly expressed my thoughts and listened to the doctor's advice.
I just need to do some tests and found out that I have mild anxiety disorder and a slight thyroid problem, which requires treatment.</p>
<p>When I was filling out the blood draw form, the nurse looked at me with a compassionate gaze, and the one who was going to draw blood sighed directly upon seeing me. However, she still gently inserted the needle and instructed me on how to position my hand so that the blood would come out faster. As for me, I calmly looked into their eyes.</p>
<p>During the super-electroencephalogram procedure, I felt like a puppet, manipulated and moved around. I suppose there will be many similar experiences in the future.</p>
<p>Today is peaceful because I know I am doing the right thing.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Azure Pan</name>
            <email>azurepan213@gmail.com</email>
            <uri>https://github.com/azurepx</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coming out]]></title>
        <id>https://azurepx.com/2023/10/16/coming-out</id>
        <link href="https://azurepx.com/2023/10/16/coming-out"/>
        <updated>2023-10-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I have been mentally exhausted, so I tried coming out to a friend, hoping it would make me feel a little better.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Recently, I have been mentally exhausted, so I tried coming out to a friend, hoping it would make me feel a little better.</p>
<p>To my surprise, when I told her everything with a nervous heart, she immediately accepted it.</p>
<div class="codeBlockContainer_Ckt0 theme-code-block" style="--prism-color:#393A34;--prism-background-color:#f6f8fa"><div class="codeBlockContent_biex"><pre tabindex="0" class="prism-code language-text codeBlock_bY9V thin-scrollbar" style="color:#393A34;background-color:#f6f8fa"><code class="codeBlockLines_e6Vv"><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">"Are you referring to being trans woman like Jinxin?"</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">"Yes."</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">"Have you made up your mind?"</span><br></span><span class="token-line" style="color:#393A34"><span class="token plain">"I have."</span><br></span></code></pre><div class="buttonGroup__atx"><button type="button" aria-label="Copy code to clipboard" title="Copy" class="clean-btn"><span class="copyButtonIcons_eSgA" aria-hidden="true"><svg viewBox="0 0 24 24" class="copyButtonIcon_y97N"><path fill="currentColor" d="M19,21H8V7H19M19,5H8A2,2 0 0,0 6,7V21A2,2 0 0,0 8,23H19A2,2 0 0,0 21,21V7A2,2 0 0,0 19,5M16,1H4A2,2 0 0,0 2,3V17H4V3H16V1Z"></path></svg><svg viewBox="0 0 24 24" class="copyButtonSuccessIcon_LjdS"><path fill="currentColor" d="M21,7L9,19L3.5,13.5L4.91,12.09L9,16.17L19.59,5.59L21,7Z"></path></svg></span></button></div></div></div>
<p>Later, we talked a lot. I shared my experiences from childhood, when I realized my gender identity, how I discovered my differences, how I hid myself, what kind of people I like, why I moved out of the school dormitory, taking a break from school, giving up, and finally having an awakening. Gradually, I started feeling much better.</p>
<p>When you have a goal, you have to live your life well, understand yourself, and be brave enough to face the world. I hope I can be a better person in the future.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Azure Pan</name>
            <email>azurepan213@gmail.com</email>
            <uri>https://github.com/azurepx</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time]]></title>
        <id>https://azurepx.com/2018/11/08/time</id>
        <link href="https://azurepx.com/2018/11/08/time"/>
        <updated>2018-11-08T09:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't have time === It's not a priority.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I don't have time === It's not a priority.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Azure Pan</name>
            <email>azurepan213@gmail.com</email>
            <uri>https://github.com/azurepx</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>